[{"answer": "I don't know on that.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Where do you feel this debate now is in America?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "I hope to achieve, for people to be responsible fully for what weapons they own.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "What do you hope to achieve by what happens tomorrow?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "It actually makes me feel more safe.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Yes, but why do you want your pizzeria full of people armed to the teeth?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "It makes me feel more safe because these are responsible people.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "They're innocent until they're proven guilty.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "So people who could walk on their own two feet and who can drive a car are not mentally ill or criminals?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I think it's being eroded.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "-- to the Second Amendment?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Personally, I don't know them.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Do you know anybody that he's asked to remove their gun, to confiscate their gun?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, the thing is I don't trust our government.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "You are quite happy for American civilians to march into your restaurant with rocket launchers, arriving in armed tanks and perhaps carrying a few Uzi submachine guns, is that your position?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, it really isn't our government that I'm worried about, it's something bigger than our government.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "How are they going to do that, with the American military or without the American military?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "I'm not saying they are going to do that.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Which part of the world do you imagine is right now marshaling its troops to invade America?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I couldn't tell you a number on that.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "How many of your customers share your views, do you think?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I am trying to make money because that will -- how it's supposed to work is I can save money, and then I could use it later in life to support me when I put my work into society.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "And that's why you're doing it, to make money, isn't it?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Zero.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "How many people have been shot in your restaurant since you've owned it?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not saying I agree that justifiable homicides have increased.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "I mean, putting aside this particular case, wouldn't you as a compassionate lawyer just feel that this is just not working?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "First of all, we're countering it by trying to get out more of the information that should have been out at the beginning.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Do you feel in the end that it will be seen as that once the trial has been and gone?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "I believe so.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Are you confident from everything that you know that in the end George Zimmerman will be seen not to have done that?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well, listen, this is a triple-X-rated case.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "-- and now suddenly is gripping everyone, what do you make of it?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, let's take a listen to some of the stuff today, which was pretty gruesome, compelling, whatever you want to call it.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "So is she really doing a disservice to all women who are truly battered, Piers?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "I don't think that aspect of him is beautiful at all.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Do you think somebody who masturbates to pictures of little boys is beautiful on the inside, right?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "It says, \"Travis, you're beautiful on the inside and out,\" doesn't it?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "To facilitate our activities.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "You were the one that had the KY or brought it into the relationship to make it better, right?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, when he jizzes on my face and throws candy my way and walks away without a word, it kind of feels like I was a prostitute.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Which one is it?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "No, I don't think you're missing anything at all.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "But am I missing something?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "It is appalling, Piers.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "This is the point that I think will anger many women, is that if she is lying through her back teeth, using the cover of somehow being this poor innocent victim of a domestically violent man is really appalling, isn't it?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "You know, there are two issues that are really being presented at the same time.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Are they damaging their case by putting her up there for too long?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, she is very mesmerizing.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Would we be going even remotely as far as we are if she wasn't there on our television screens, do you think?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "That's what the jurors basically are going to have to decide.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "It comes down to this, is this guy just fantasizing or is there enough evidence to suggest he was really planning to do this?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Well, I teach about these cases in my criminal law class and I write about them.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Because in reality if they cannot prove that he was genuinely going to do this, then presumably he will walk, won't he?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "LLRED: Not really just to worry them, but having said that --", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Let me bring in Gloria there, because it seems to me that even if he wasn't going to carry out these appalling crimes, the mere fact he's put these women, including his wife and female friends, through this appalling psychological trauma, that they must be reading about this sickening plot that he was e-mailing people about, is that not in itself a crime?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "There are more details.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Isn't that abuse to his wife?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "You know, it was five years pretty much from beginning to end.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Wasn't it?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's tough.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What is your reaction to the reaction so far?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I think that's always true.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "But did you think that the president had a point there, that perhaps the Canadians in the movie version didn't get quite enough of the credit they probably deserved?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I'm always ready to jump in there.", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Do you think that your husband deserves all the adulation that's being showered upon him?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "130226pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 554}]